drive faster
开得更快
An Qiu
安秋
Why
为什么
Why only avenge my relatives?
为什么只为我的亲人报仇？
i can't even do that
我什至做不到
Is it because you changed my original obsession?
是因为你改变了我最初的执念吗？
That's why I can't move my hands
这就是为什么我的手无法动弹
An Qiu
安秋
why can't you
你为什么不能
Break through the original obsession again?
再次突破最初的执念？
You know what I hate most?
你知道我最讨厌什么吗？
Just give us hope
只要给我们希望
Then I was disappointed again
然后又让我失望了
you betrayed my trust
你背叛了我的信任
betray my love
背叛我的爱
What's the difference between you and Luo Su?
你和罗苏有什么区别？
You are wrong
您错了
Russell never betrayed you
罗素从未背叛过你
I met the owner of Dreamland Club
我遇见了梦境俱乐部的老板
Luo Su actually has always loved you
罗苏其实一直爱着你
Luosu Betrays Dreamland Club
罗苏背叛梦境俱乐部
Russell's early obsessions
罗素早年的痴迷
Be loyal to the realm of dreams
忠于梦想的境界
He's like a stubborn dog
他就像一只顽固的狗
I couldn't even kick him out.
我什至无法把他踢出去。
It is precisely because of this
也正是因为如此
He recruited a lot of androids
他招募了很多仿生人
I always feel
我总觉得
There's certainly nothing wrong with the initial obsession
最初的痴迷肯定不会有问题
Until I met Yin Tianhong
直到遇见殷天鸿
Yin Tianhong took the initiative to come to the dreamland for me
殷天红主动为了我来到梦境
Actually I don't want him to come
其实我不想让他来
Can you come and tell him?
你能过来告诉他吗？
let him go
放了他
You asked me to say that
你让我这么说
This club is a charity
这个俱乐部是一个慈善机构
I am
我是
I'm not paying you less than you should.
我给你的钱并没有比你应该付的少。
I
我
and
而且
Who told me to stay?
谁叫我留下来的？
You are the boss, I know you have the kindest heart
你是老板，我知道你有一颗最善良的心
But I couldn't resist the initial obsession
但我无法抗拒最初的痴迷
Boss, do you think this is okay?
老板，你觉得这样可以吗？
You tell him to go
你告诉他走
Then I will find more for you
然后我会为你找到更多
Better servers are coming
更好的服务器即将到来
I promise
我保证
then tell me
然后告诉我
why do you want him to leave
你为什么要他走
he is a good man
他是一个好人
depends on you
取决于你
You just hide your original obsession
你只是隐藏了最初的痴迷
He just tricked her into the dream world
他才把她骗进了梦境世界
Do you think you're doing that now?
你认为你现在正在这样做吗？
Will he thank you?
他会感谢你吗？
He will just think you are a liar
他只会认为你是个骗子
no problem
没问题
It doesn't matter what he thinks
他怎么想并不重要
He doesn't even need to know
他甚至不需要知道
As long as he is no longer too tired
只要他不再太累
Yin Tianhong is this person
殷天鸿就是这个人
Accident
意外
If you are really moved,
如果你真的被感动了，
you are in danger
你有危险
I won't help you open this mouth
我不会帮你张开这张嘴
Does he want to stay?
他想留下来吗？
That's his own business
那是他自己的事
I don’t know if Luo Su was initially obsessed with this.
不知道罗苏最初是不是痴迷于此
Still trapped by my own heart
依然被自己的心所困
He took the initiative to let Yin Tianhong go
他主动放走了殷天鸿
He actually set a trap to stimulate it
他居然设下陷阱来刺激它
I'm just kidding you
我只是和你开玩笑
let you go now
现在让你走
Never go back to dreamland again
再也不会回到梦乡
You said you killed the robot
你说你杀了机器人
It’s to release their original obsession
是为了释放他们最初的执念
But Russell never
但罗素从来没有
Imprisoned by his true obsession
被他真正的痴迷所囚禁
He sets a trap for you to leave the dreamland
他设下陷阱让你离开梦境
He's always protecting you, you know?
他一直在保护你，你知道吗？
you are talking nonsense
你在胡说八道
He obviously did it out of initial obsession
他这么做显然是出于最初的痴迷
betray me
背叛我
I can see that you are very stubborn.
看得出来你很固执
You can never truly trust others
你永远不会真正信任别人
if not
如果不
How could you be deceived by Luo Su so easily?
你怎么这么容易就被罗苏骗了？
How could you not know that he wanted to save you?
你怎么会不知道他是想救你呢？
Have you said enough?
你说够了吗？
you think you are god
你以为你是神
In fact, you are just a coward with low self-esteem.
其实，你只是一个自卑的胆小鬼。
Even you underestimate yourself
连你自己都低估了
I didn't, I didn't
我没有，我没有
Then why don't you dare to kill someone?
那你为什么不敢杀人呢？
Is this the lowest cost to shut down android?
这是关闭android的最低成本吗？
Yin Tianhong
Yin Tianhong
I'm not a person who dares not face myself
我不是一个不敢面对自己的人
that is you
那是你
Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo
You have no right to say this to him.
你没有权利对他说这些。
Yin Tianhong
Yin Tianhong
calm
冷静的
Why
为什么
Why is he still lying to me?
他为什么还要骗我？
because he loves you
因为他爱你
That's why he wants to save you
这就是他想救你的原因
I know you love him too
我知道你也爱他
That's why you're in so much pain right now
这就是为什么你现在如此痛苦
halo
光环
Halo Zhou Qi
Halo Zhou Qi
Wan Guofeng
Wan Guofeng
The suspect has taken hostages
目前嫌疑人已劫持人质
It doesn't matter if he's a robot or not.
他是不是机器人并不重要
handle all of this
处理所有这些
I want to trouble you now
我现在就想麻烦你
Cooperate with external work
配合外部工作
Now we take over here
现在我们接管了这里
Clear
清除
Do you still remember our agreement?
你还记得我们的约定吗？
we'll leave here together
我们将一起离开这里
leave
离开
lay down your weapons
放下你的武器
An Qiu
安秋
leave
离开
calm
冷静的
direct
直接的
This world cannot tolerate us
这个世界容不下我们
accustomed to
惯于
Don't shoot
别开枪
He has hostages
他有人质
please leave
请离开
I said don't shoot
我说别开枪
Yin Tianhong
Yin Tianhong
Can you put the knife down?
你能把刀放下吗？
An Qiu
安秋
you don't have to keep living
你不必继续生活
Bear the pain of being deceived
承受着被欺骗的痛苦
Yin Tianhong, stop being stubborn.
殷天鸿，你别再固执了。
Let me help you, okay?
让我帮你，好吗？
Yin Tianhong
Yin Tianhong
You can't make decisions for me
你不能替我做决定
i will accompany you
我会陪伴你
Yin Tianhong is dead
尹天鸿死了
It's because of hatred
是因为仇恨
also because of love
也因为爱
Maybe he's been confused
也许他一直很困惑
because he doesn't know
因为他不知道
my highest emotion
我最高的情感
what on earth is that
那到底是什么
So he only felt pain
所以他只觉得痛苦
He can't realize it either
他也无法意识到
The image that has always been etched in his mind
一直铭刻在他脑海中的形象
symbolic
象征化的
In fact, this is life and hope
其实这就是生命和希望
Cheng Nuo, how are you?
程诺，你怎么样？
Di mana An Qiu?
Di mana An Qiu?
in the waiting room
在候诊室
An Qiu
安秋
sorry
对不起
But it's dangerous for you to stay here
但你留在这里很危险
They will definitely say that
他们肯定会这么说
Hide your identity and walk into bright eyes
隐藏身份，走进明亮的双眸
Then I'll take this opportunity to punish you.
那就趁这个机会惩罚你吧
continue
继续
you must go with me
你必须跟我一起去
I will definitely find a way to save you
我一定会找到办法来拯救你
I won't go with you
我不会和你一起去
An Qiu
安秋
Do not do
不要做
i would rather be punished
我宁愿受到惩罚
I no longer want to be a tool dependent on the pity of others.
我不想再成为依赖他人怜悯的工具。
I know you hate Mingmou
我知道你讨厌明谋
He hates me more and more
越来越讨厌我了
But can you give up on yourself?
但你能不能放弃自己呢？
There is still hope
仍有希望
You hope that I will continue to work hard and succeed.
你希望我继续努力并成功
failed experiment
失败的实验
Or those who harm their own kind?
还是那些伤害自己同类的人？
An Qiu
安秋
you're right
你说得对
I hate you
我恨你
But I hate myself even more
但我更讨厌自己
hate myself for being weak
恨自己软弱
fail
失败
I hate fate too
我也讨厌命运
Please introduce yourself
介绍一下你自己吧
An Qiu, I'm sorry
安秋，对不起
let me beg you
让我求你
leave here
离开这里
don't let me see you again
别让我再见到你
Can you please not take An Qiu away?
你能不能不要把安秋带走？
I beg you
我求求你
An Qiu asked you to come
安秋叫你来
No
不
He doesn't need my help
他不需要我的帮助
Then why do you insist on saving him?
那你为什么还要坚持救他呢？
Although An Qiu is a bionic person,
虽然安秋是一个仿生人，
But he is no different from us
但他和我们没有什么不同
I know
我知道
An Qiu's situation is very miserable
安秋的处境很悲惨
But he is a robot and we have bright eyes
但他是一个机器人，我们有明亮的眼睛
we have our responsibilities
我们有我们的责任
In this case, do we have no other choice?
既然如此，我们就没有别的选择了吗？
I can't do anything now
我现在什么也做不了
Do you know how many pairs of eyes there are out there?
你知道外面有多少双眼睛吗？
Are you watching us?
你在看着我们吗？
Something big happened last night
昨晚发生了一件大事
Everyone knows An Qiu’s identity
安秋的身份大家都知道了
if no action is taken
如果不采取任何措施
So how should we give an explanation to the outside world?
那么我们该如何给外界一个交代呢？
minister
部长
An Qiu comes from my mother's laboratory
安秋来自我妈妈的实验室
Bionic research objects
仿生研究对象
My mother's death may have something to do with him
我母亲的死可能与他有关
if he is fired
如果他被开除
The truth about my mother's death
关于我母亲去世的真相
It could be lost forever.
它可能会永远失去。
So please
所以，请
even for my mother
即使是为了我的母亲
You don't want him to die in an unknown way, right?
你也不希望他以一种未知的方式死去吧？
There is currently no evidence of this
目前还没有证据表明这一点
An Qiu is related to your mother's case
安秋和你母亲的案子有关
If you can connect two things together
如果你能将两件事连接在一起
perhaps
或许
we can defer disposal
我们可以推迟处置
give me some more time
再给我一些时间
I will definitely find it
我一定会找到的
halo
光环
I am Wan Guofeng
我是万国锋
There are still doubts about the Anqiu case.
安丘案至今仍存在疑点。
Need clarification
需要澄清
see if you can
看看你能不能
postpone it for a few more days
再推迟几天
Understood
明白了
Your mother and I are old classmates
我和你妈妈是老同学
He said before that he wanted to rent this place from me
他之前说过要向我租这个地方
research
进行研究
There was always a girl by his side at that time
那时他身边一直有一个女孩
It turned out to be Anqiu
原来是安丘
Are they just the two of them?
难道只有他们两个人吗？
of
的
It seems that the two chat frequently.
看来两人经常聊天。
I think we get along well
我觉得我们相处得很好
after
之后
Your mother also introduced him to our internship.
你妈妈还介绍他到我们这里实习。
Strong working ability and good performance
工作能力很强，表现也很好
everything is here
所有的东西都在这里
We haven't moved yet
我们还没搬家
Take the time to see for yourself
花点时间亲自看看
The first time was June 5th
第一次是6月5日
Halo Anqing
光环安庆
I am Zhang Ye
我是张也
people engaged in psychological research
从事心理学研究的人
Nice to meet you
很高兴认识你
How do you get a good rest?
你怎样休息好？
I see your skin is slowly recovering.
我看到你的皮肤正在慢慢恢复。
why am i here
为什么我在这里
What's left
剩下的呢
he is there
他在那
The purpose of our experiment is
我们实验的目的是
Get over your initial obsession with Android
摆脱最初对 Android 的痴迷
and psychological counseling
和心理咨询
Then I chose you
然后我选择了你
I hope we can work together
我希望我们能一起努力
why me
为什么是我
Why did you ask me out alone?
你为什么约我单独出去？
perhaps
或许
Your initial obsession has failed
你最初的痴迷已经失败
Of course this is just my guess
当然这只是我的猜测
Don't worry, I won't force you
你放心，我不会强迫你的
Take a good rest first
先好好休息一下
do what you want
做你想做的事
if you need anything you can tell me
如果你需要什么，你可以告诉我
Then let's go here first today
那我们今天就先到这里吧
Thanks
谢谢
It's over the first time
第一次就结束了
To avoid unnecessary problems
以免出现不必要的问题
Can I call you Anqiu from now on?
从现在开始我就叫你安丘好不好？
During this process
在这个过程中
I may have to ask you a lot of questions
我可能要问你很多问题
You may also receive some medications
您可能还会接受一些药物治疗
if you don't want to do this
如果你不想这样做
you can reject me anytime
你可以随时拒绝我
it's definitely my fault
这绝对是我的错
the only thing you have to do
你唯一要做的事
stay true to yourself
保持自己的本性
An Qiu
安秋
Are you OK
你好吗
minister
部长
why are you here
你为什么在这
I finally found you
我终于找到你了
you are that person
你就是那个人
Zhang Ya’s hidden bionic man
张雅隐藏的仿生人
Do you know Zhang Ya?
你知道张雅吗？
An idea to break away from the initial obsession with android
一个摆脱最初对 android 痴迷的想法
He was the one who made the suggestion
他是提出这个建议的人
Although I am working in Mingmou
虽然我在明谋工作
But over the years
但这些年来
I think humans are cruel to robots
我认为人类对机器人很残忍
In fact, robots and humans
事实上，机器人和人类
no difference
没有任何区别
What is your relationship with Ming?
你和明某是什么关系？
It should be said that we have a cooperative relationship
应该说我们是合作关系
We do a lot of things with android
我们用 android 做了很多事情
A very important psychological experiment
一个非常重要的心理实验
so
所以
When Zhang Ya proposed this plan to me,
当张雅向我提出这个计划时，
I think this is a turning point
我认为这是一个转折点
If the original obsession could be replaced
如果最初的执念可以被取代
even removed
甚至被移除
This will help you better integrate into society
这会让你更好地融入社会
live well
生活得很好
able
能
Are you living your life on your own terms?
你是按照自己的意愿生活吗？
certainly
当然
Humans are the ones who created us
人类是创造我们的人
It is also humans who destroy us
毁灭我们的也是人类
What is being saved now is humanity.
现在拯救的是人类。
If a mother
如果一个母亲
He doesn't love his children at all
他根本不爱他的孩子
Then why did she give birth to him?
那她为什么要生他呢？
at first i thought
起初我以为
we have the same goal
我们有同一个目标
But as the experiment progresses
但随着实验的进展
I feel like the gap between us is getting bigger and bigger
我觉得我们之间的差距越来越大
Zhang Ya told me she found it
张雅告诉我她找到了
perfect test subject
完美的测试对象
I asked him who he was, but he wouldn't tell me.
我问他是谁，他不告诉我。
I've felt it ever since
从那时起我就感受到了
He has other plans
他还有其他计划
My current relationship with my children
我目前与孩子的关系
not too good
不太好
Then I have no choice
那我别无选择
no way to communicate
没有办法沟通
yes
是
Relationship with Cheng Nuo
与程诺的关系
this is always bad
这总是不好的
He wants to change his initial obsession with robots
他要改变对机器人最初的执念
Let them become researchers
让他们成为研究人员
at first i thought
起初我以为
This is what scientists insist on
这就是科学家的坚持
But then I found out
但后来我发现
This is his confession to his son
这是他对自己儿子的告白
maybe because i don't know
也许因为我不知道
How to express your love for each other
如何表达对彼此的爱
maybe we missed it
也许我们错过了
ability to love
爱的能力
That
那
That's just because you're human
那只是因为你是人类
my early obsession
我早年的痴迷
This is to protect your family and the family that loves you
这是为了保护你的家人和爱你的家人
So after Anyang died
所以安阳死后
I don't even know who to love anymore
我什至不知道该爱谁了
I don’t even have the original obsession
我连最初的执念都没有
If it is Android
如果是安卓的话
Not even his initial obsession.
甚至连他最初的痴迷都没有
What is the meaning of my life?
我的人生还有什么意义呢？
An Qiu
安秋
What I want to tell you is
我想告诉你的是
Our sorrow is justified
我们的悲伤是有道理的
we have the right to grieve
我们有权利悲伤
Even if you lose your original obsession
即使你失去了最初的执念
We can still find a way out together
我们仍然可以找到共同的出路
So he wants to do it
所以他想要做到
You can stay with Cheng Nuo
你可以留在程诺身边
obey him completely and protect his people
完全服从他并保护他的人民
when needed
当需要的时候
can sacrifice for him
可以为他牺牲
scissors, paper, rock
剪刀、布、石头
We played chess until late last night
昨晚我们下棋直到深夜
I do not remember
我不记得了
Recently taken reagents
最近服用过试剂
Do you feel sick?
你觉得不舒服吗？
I've been dreaming about it lately
我最近一直梦见它
I have a brother
我有个兄弟
But this dream is getting blurry
但这个梦越来越模糊
I dreamed that we lived in the same room
我梦见我们住在一个房间里
in an abandoned house
在一座废弃的房子里
Living conditions are very difficult
生活条件非常艰苦
but very happy
但很高兴
He did it
他做到了
He protected his murderous son very well.
很好的保护了自己的杀人儿子
he seems to have done it
他似乎做到了
Tapi An Qiu
Tapi An Qiu
We still have a chance to change this
我们仍然有机会改变这一点
Your initial obsession has changed
你最初的痴迷已经改变
This is a fact
这是事实
but in you
但在你身上
Have neurons that can save other robots
拥有可以拯救其他机器人的神经元
but I
但是我
Is there any way to extract it for you?
有办法帮你提取吗？
Sorry to ask you suddenly
抱歉刚才突然问你
Is there anything wrong with the previous experiment?
难道之前的实验有什么问题吗？
it has nothing to do with you
这与你无关
This is between me and my partner
这是我和我的伴侣之间的事
I'm afraid he wants
我怕他想要
Tips for getting rid of initial distress
消除最初困扰的技巧
suitable for humans
适用于人类
He wants to control human emotions
他想控制人类的情绪
you want
你想要
Do you still believe in humans?
你还相信人类吗？
He wants to extract the neurons in your body
他想提取你体内的神经元
create an android
创建一个安卓
Pandora's box has been opened
潘多拉魔盒已被打开
I won't allow him to open a second one
我不会允许他打开第二个
What can I do for you?
我能为您做些什么？
you don't need to do anything
你不需要做任何事
This is your last injection
这是您最后一次注射
I might increase the dose
我可能会增加剂量
The goal is to protect you
目标是保护你
When you wake up you might forget who I am
当你醒来时你可能会忘记我是谁
You will lose your previous memories
你会失去以前的记忆
But it doesn't matter
但这并不重要
I will prepare background information for you
我会为你准备背景资料
and where you work and study
以及您工作和学习的地方
You also forget that you are a robot
你也会忘记你是一个机器人
Wait until you open your eyes again
等到你再次睁开眼睛
This is the new you
这就是新的你
I do not want to forget you
我不想忘记你
Even if you forget me
就算你忘记我
I also know you will become one of them
我也知道你会成为他们中的一员
Very very good psychiatrist
非常非常好的心理医生
I won't tell him everything about you
我不会告诉他关于你的一切